{
    "id": "2b62b3608cb94b78a5fca42f29a9f638",
    "title": "Gerund Or Infinitive",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I still remember …………. my first car.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to buy",
                "buying"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Don’t forget …………………. the door when you leave.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "locking",
                "to lock"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I enjoyed ……………… the movie.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "watching",
                "to watch"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She avoided ………………… them because she was in a hurry to leave.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "meeting",
                "to meet"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You promised ………………… me a diamond necklace for my birthday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to buy",
                "buying"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She has agreed ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to come",
                "coming"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I thanked them ………………… me out.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to help",
                "for helping"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I expect him …………….. at 4 o’clock.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "calling",
                "to call"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Would you like ………………… with us?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "coming",
                "to come"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t feel like ……………… it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "doing",
                "to do"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}